Everyone is definitely not going to be in my scene.
There is probably 10
people in there.
I'm here.
We are heading to the airport right now, and we're going to fly to LA for the Apple Apple towards Sarah.
Okay,
so
I've decided to shower and just freshen up after that flight because I always feel so disgusting after I fly.
I have to shower.
So now I'm just getting ready.
It's still pretty early in the day.
It's only 1:24, but because we're now three hours behind, I am feeling so incredibly hangry.
I was crashing up before my shower because I just couldn't decide if I wanted to shower or if I should eat and then get all ready again
and then go out to eat, or if I should just go eat something in the meantime.
But then I don't like showering right after a meal because I feel like it always upsets my stomach.
Long story short, I decided to shower because I felt like that would make me feel the best.
And now I'm just rushing to get my makeup done so then I can go eat.
I think I'm going to go to Air One or Raising Cane's.
Obviously very different price points and different kinds of food.
But I'm just going to see what's in the area.
I'm going to go to West Hollywood.
And yeah, let me give you a hotel tour.
This is obviously the bathroom.
This is just the vanity where I got ready.
And then this is the outfit that I pulled that I'm going to wear today.
It's kind of giving Miu Miu, but the pieces are from Sweet Chilling.
And this is just what the room looks like.
Just got some shoes laid out.
My airport outfit is hanging.
Obviously took one of the robes to put on because I love a hotel robe.
This is so good.
Wow.
I'm actually very surprised.
Okay, and then I have the matcha with the cloud foam top.
This is the one that Ainsley recommended.
I'm trying to see which one I like better, but I'm honestly really surprised by this one.
This is really so much caffeine to have like the Earl, Ice Banner, and the matcha cream top, but they're both so good.
Actually, I'm so surprised.
Like you guys know, I don't usually drink a lot of coffee, but this is so fire.
I've just left Community Goods and I'm walking down Fairfax Avenue now.
It is so busy, but honestly, I'm really loving this walk because the skies are crystal clear, the sun is out, and I just feel like I've completely
escaped the winter blues.
But now I walking towards the Grove because I heard that there is a two at Brandy Melville that just opened and also an Air One.
And I just haven eaten in over 12 hours.
Air one is definitely not going to be my scene.
But I still want to check it out and see what it going to be like.
What is this?
Okay, we have made it out of Air One.
That was a successful run, I think.
I got the Hailey Bieber smoothie.
This was 20 USD.
So, I ended up getting a combo plate.
So, this is the miso black cod.
It's honestly a decent size.
Brought to me in an old school at Mac and Cheese.
There is probably 10 noodles in there.
But everything does actually smell pretty good.
And this entire plate was 28 USD.
But AppleBully on a meal stipend.
So, thank you to the Apple team.
I feel like we need to try the smoothie first.
This is the strawberry glaze maybe?
This is just a strawberry spread.
Some really nice yogurt, but that's about it.
Let's try this cod though.
Mmm, that is really good.
It
is literally a winter wonderland here,
minus the snow, but there's so many decorations.
There are definitely more decorations here than there are downtown, but I'm about to head into the rainy Melville now because I couldn't go in with my
drink, so I just finished it while browsing and yeah!
So
bead embroidery ranch that is so American.
There's even dill pickle ornament that's cute.
Oh my gosh, these towels are so pretty.
Look at this one.
Oh my god, this is like a better Marshalls and Winners.
We're at Soho House for dinner.
And Kush, my manager, is a member.
And so we're just headed up there now.
This is a very interesting elevator.
Kind of reminds me of a couch.
In the nicest way.
Also wow there so many.
Flyways, I'm back at the hotel now, at dinner with the Spark team.
It was so amazing.
I'm officially back from my big day out in LA.
It was so much fun.
I hope you guys had fun tagging along with me.
I'm just gonna get ready for bed now.
And I actually forgot my favorite makeup remover at home, at home, so I actually popped into a Sephora and I just picked up this travel size Clinique
Take the Day Off Cleansing Balm.
I hope it's good.
I think I saw a bunch of people recommend it on TikTok in the past, or it's just like a common favorite.
Yeah, also spent another day in these three to four inch stompers from Jonak.
I actually got a lot of comments on them today, and yeah, let's get ready for bed, and then we're gonna have another big day tomorrow.
Clearly, I am not as type A as I thought I was because I don't have a single pair of pajamas packed in my luggage.
So I've just put on another one of these bathrobes.
That's the one I put on while I was getting ready after my shower.
So this one's all clean and fresh for sleep.
Yeah, I'm just going to take my makeup off now.
Guys, I also have these little wristbands that stop the water from running down your forearm when you're washing your face.
So we're going to see if they work, and I'm also going to use this cleansing balm, and I also hope that it works because I'm wearing a
ton of makeup right now.
Anyone else hand you off their makeup?
I just want to go to bed.
Also, always wash your hands before you take off your makeup.
I have no idea if this is enough.
Maybe a little emulsify it.
A little bit of water.
These wristbands don't work.
I can feel the water splashing on my toes.
Things don't work.
Oh my god, you guys, this is a mess.
This is literally such a mess, and then water is actually indeed gripping down my wrist.
Look at this.
I don't know how to wash my face clearly because what the heck.
Look, that was not helpful.
This is actually not that bad.
This is brand approved.
Time for skincare.
Okay, that is my nighttime skincare all done.
I am gonna do some eye patches in a bed though.
Yay, we're having a slumber party together.
Hi guys, it is day two of LA, and I've just gotten ready into like something smart casual, and I'm gonna put on these little heels to complete
my look because now I'm actually headed out to the Google YouTube office to meet my friend Angelica.
We've been online friends for so many years now, and she said I could join her at the office for some lunch, so yeah, let me show you
guys the fit.
Okay, and this is the outfit.
My top is from Addicted, these are some Aritzia pants, and then I just have on these Jonak kitten heels.
Yeah, let's get going.
Oh my gosh, I think the office is similar to a college dorm.
Yes, I love it.
It looks so good.
The real tech experience.
Guys,
I'm a little salty because this is my section's micro kitchen, but it's also next to the lunch area, so everybody takes from this.
It's like the communal one, and the no, but it looks dog.
No, this is like this.
It's gonna go away soon.
The protein bars I like are gone.
The hot Cheetos are gone, but we have Dusters, and these wafer things are yummy.
I love these.
Gummy bears are really good.
The Albany's one, no, the best here.
Hi!
We just ended a little tour lunch at the Google YouTube office in LA.
Yes!
It is so nice in here.
What's your reaction?
It's really spacious.
I feel like I need to work in tech.
Yes.
Leave my job.
Exactly.
New job and new career.
Literally, I would come work and be your coworker.
I feel like, you know what they show in movies?
Yeah.
They're like mocking tech workers.
I feel like it's real.
No, it is real.
No, it is real, like you see everybody working, there's a coffee bar, we saw the snacks, there's a gaming room, people bring their
dogs, like it's like, I promise we all work really hard, and it's actually good.
Yeah, period.
And now for the reason why I'm in LA.
I went to the Apple App Store Awards, which is basically where Apple highlights and celebrates some of the apps and their founders that really stood out this
year.
There are Different categories, there are different winners, and it just felt like it was the Oscar for apps in a way.
We have made it to the Apple App Awards.
We're gonna just check out a bunch of different apps and their creators and see what they won, and yeah, there are so many people here.
I'm so excited.
And then we went on inside, and one of the first apps we saw was Pokemon TCG Pocket, which is a mobile game where you collect digital Pokemon
cards, battle, and trade with friends.
And Loki unlocked so much nostalgia for me.
And then obviously, I had to check out the productivity section, where I met the developer behind Focus Friend, Bria.
I learned that it's just her and Hank Green behind this app, and the fact that they've only been out for a few months and won the Cultural
Impact Award was so cool.
Also, Hank Green was there, so as a STEM girly who grew up on Crash Course, this was a very full circle moment for me.
I had to take a picture.
And now I talk a lot about timers and gamifying studying on my channel, so this app is the perfect combination of both.
It locks down distracting apps on your phone so you can't doom scroll, and motivates you to use up your entire focus timer so your little character finishes
its knitting, and then you can decorate their apartment.
I also went to go hear a little bit from Strava, which is fun because I am a proud Half Marathon supporter.
I cannot run, but I've been to quite a few now just to cheer on my friends, so getting to chat with their team and hear about how
they're building community was really cool.
One thing I didn't know before was HBO Max now has ASL support, where you can see an interpreter on the screen while watching.
I just thought this was really meaningful and a good reminder of how tech can keep moving, but in a more inclusive direction.
And overall, it was just a really cool experience getting to be around so many creatives and then innovative people doing what they love.
One of my favorite pastimes is hearing what people are passionate about in their passion projects.
So yeah, thank you to Apple.
Hello!
Okay, yes!
Be productive, be healthy, be happy!
Drink water!
Wow!
Such a big sis!
Oh my gosh, sorry!
Thank you so much!
Aisha and I are leaving the event now.
It was so fun!
We had so much fun!
And it is literally so dark out now.
We were in there for three hours.
Three hours.
Yeah.
Thank you.